When we create resources in one region,
当我们在一个地区创造资源时
they only appear in that one region.
它们只出现在那个区域
For example, as we can see,
例如 我们可以看到
we've got an EC2 instance in the Ohio region.
我们在俄亥俄地区有个 EC2 的实例
If we switch to another region,
如果我们切换到另一个区域
we will see that that instance is no longer visible.
我们就会看到这个实例已经看不起来了
This happens because we have to manage most resources within AWS on a per region basis.
发生这种情况的原因是 我们必须根据每个区域管理 AWS 内部的大部分资源
A few of the AWS global services,
一些 AWS 全球服务
such as IAM or Cloudfront are managed on a global scale.
例如  IAM 或 Cloudfront 在全球范围内进行管理
But all of these individual services,
但所有这些个人服务
most services within AWS,
AWS 中的大部分服务
you must pay attention to which region you're looking at.
你一定要注意你要看哪个区域